Manoj Thapa

London, England, United Kingdom

genjithapa182@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/manoj-thapa-3475a21a1

Summary

Hi, I am Manoj Kumar Thapa, a web developer focused on crafting great web experiences. Designing and Coding have been my passion since the days I started working with computers but I found myself into web design/development since 2017. I enjoy creating beautifully designed, intuitive and functional websites.

For over past 5 years, I have worked in many different fields. I have also recently been studying to become a web developer and have great passion for it. Studying web developemt has enhanced my abilities in writing clean sementic code, browser testing, mobile responsiveness, user friendly and designing web pages based upon its target audience.

Experience

Chef De Partie

Restaurant Associates UK

2020 - 2021 (2 years)

- Ensuring foods are prepared promptly on a tight schedule while adhering to food safety standards.
- Capable of handling sections alone and making proper decisions for the best interest of the company.
- Stock rotation and management to maximize output and minimize wastage.

Chef

The Ritz-Carlton Hotel Company, L.L.C.

2015 - 2017 (3 years)

- Proper loading and unloading of delivery from supplier in minimum amount of time to ensure quality of goods.
- Managing junior staffs to maximize quality of work is delivered.
- Deal with customers where required to be the face of the company.
- Proper time management.
- Able to do heavy lifting as required.
- Able to calmly prepare and cook meals in a busy and high pressure environment.

Education

Rouxbe Online Cooking School, Bahrain

Rouxbe Online Cooking School in Culinary Foundations, Culinary Arts and Related Services

2016 - 2016

From the course, I have learnt skills required in a very busy environment from basics to advance. I was taught on the food safety, proper handling of different large equipment's used in the kitchen, stock rotation, time management and stock management.

Academy of Culinary Arts & Hospitality Management, Nepal

Diploma in Culinary Arts, Culinary Arts/Chef Training 2014 - 2015

From the course, I have learnt skills required in a very busy environment from basics to advance. I was taught on the food safety, proper handling of different large equipment's used in the kitchen, stock rotation, time management and stock management.

Bartley Secondary School - Singapore

GCSE or equivalent in GCE O-Level

Jan 2004 - Dec 2008

1) English: C

2) Mathematics: B

3) Science: B

4) Principles of Accounts : B

5) Combined Humanities: C

6) Food and Nutrition: B

Licenses & Certifications

- Full-Stack Engineer Career Path CodeAcademy
- Learn jQuery Course CodeAcademy
- Learn Python 3 Course CodeAcademy
- **Learn C# Course** CodeAcademy
- **Learn Java Course** Codecademy
- Web Development Career Path CodeAcademy
- Introduction to Programming Using HTML and CSS Microsoft H942-4693

Skills

HTML5 • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • Bootstrap • JavaScript • PHP • WordPress • English • Communication • Analytical Skills • Strategy